- Well, hello there.
- Hi, I hope we're not too late.
- No, no. Perfect timing.
- Okay.
- Stan, this is my husband, Walt.
- Hi.
- Good to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Sandia Laboratories, huh?
- Yeah.
I hear some fascinating stuff
goes on out there.
Yeah, well, you know.
Working on anything
you can talk about?
I'm picturing giant space lasers.
Am I right?
Honestly, what I do
would bore you senseless.
Giant space lasers? That sounds cool.
I'll bring it up at our next staff meeting.
- Well, just remember I get a cut.
- All right. It's a deal.
So this is it, honey. What do you say?
Wanna take a tour?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Look, how about
I give ya'll some privacy?
I'll go out to the car, make a few calls.
Take as much time as you need.
- All right.
- Okay, thanks.
- He's a nice guy. He doesn't push.
- Yeah.
So as you can see,
there's this kind of flow going on here.
- It's a nice big living room.
- Yeah.
And this is the dining area.
- Oh, the dining area. Right.
- Yes. Oh, and...
...it's got a pool.
Pool is nice.
Backyard could be a little bigger.
And... Oh, there's a breakfast bar
kind of dealie here, which is nice.
And, I don't know,
the kitchen's really spacious...
...and, you know,
got good appliances and...
How many bedrooms?
Three. Told you.
They're all pretty good size and...
Oh, this is the first one here.
And then there's two more
at the back.
Only three bedrooms?
We're gonna need at least five,
don't you think?
- Five?
- Yeah.
What, do I look like
I'm about to drop a litter?
No, no, no.
We'll have three kids total, eventually.
Yeah, but we'll need
a spare room for a study...
...so that I can work at home
and you can write.
Yeah, no.
I don't think this is gonna be... enough.
Okay, what about a wine cellar?
I mean, we certainly cannot be
expected to live without a wine cellar.
Very funny. I just think we need
to set our sights high is all.
- At least, higher than here.
- Walt, this is a good neighbourhood.
It's got a good elementary
and a very good high school...
...and believe me, because I have
definitely looked everywhere.
For our price range,
this is as good as it gets.
Well, then let's stretch our price range.
Truly. I mean, why...?
Why buy a starter house when we'll
have to move out in a year or two?
Did you win the lottery
and not tell me?
I'm serious.
Come on. Why be cautious?
We've got nowhere to go but up.
- Yeah.
- Walter, you see us?
Yeah. I see you.
I'd lik e you to exit your vehicle
and start walking toward us.
And then what?
I'm gonna need some...
Some kind of assurance.
I assure you,
I could kill you from way over here...
...if it mak es you feel any better.
Walter, you've been busy.
You wanna put your arms out
to your sides for me, if you would?
You know I haven't slept
since Thursday?
I was out all night
cleaning up after you.
I need my sleep.
You said no half measures.
Yeah. Funny how words can be so open
to interpretation.
- You get your car fixed?
- Not yet.
You're gonna wanna
get your car fixed.
Let's see how this goes first.
Has your condition worsened?
- Excuse me?
- Your medical condition.
- Has it grown worse?
- Not that I know of, no.
Is there a ringing in your ears?
Are you seeing bright lights
or hearing voices?
- I'm quite well, thank you.
- No. Clearly, you are not.
No rational person would do
as you have done.
Explain yourself.
My partner was about
to get himself shot.
I inte... ned.
Some worthless junkie.
For him, you inte... ne
and put us all at risk.
Some contemptible junkie who couldn't
keep the peace for eight hours.
That's right. He couldn't.
He was angry
because those dealers of yours...
...had just murdered
an 11 -year-old boy.
I heard about it.
He should have
let me take care of them.
Maybe.
Then again, maybe he thought
it was you who gave the order.
Are you asking me
if I ordered the murder of a child?
I would never ask you that.
Where is Pinkman now?
I wouldn't know.
Couple of time zones away, at least.
Beyond that, I'd only be guessing.
He has enough money to last forever,
he knows he needs to keep moving.
You'll never find him.
I don't know, Walt...
...it's what I do, after all.
He's out of the picture.
I saved his life, I owed him that,
but now he and I are done.
Which is exactly what you wanted,
isn't it?
You've always struck me
as a very pragmatic man.
So if I may,
I would like to review options with you.
Of which, it seems to me,
you have two.
Option A:
You kill me right here and now.
Apparently,
I have made that very easy for you.
You can kill me, no witnesses...
...and then spend the next few weeks
or months...
...tracking down Jesse Pinkman
and you kill him too.
A pointless exercise, it seems to me,
but that is option A.
What is option B?
I continue cooking.
You and I both forget about Pinkman.
We forget this ever happened.
We consider this a Ione hiccup...
...in an otherwise long
and fruitful business arrangement.
I prefer option B.
You'd need a new assistant.
- I could get right on that.
- No.
This time, I choose.
Your car...
...get it fixed.
Yeah.
Really?
It's good to see you.
Thanks.
It's good to be back.
Well, shall we?
By all means, Gale, let's cook.
What about that rhinoceros?
You think he'd make a good pet?
- No.
- No?
Don't you think if you called,
he'd come running?
I bet he would.
I bet he'd come running:
You're silly, Pop-Pop.
Well, a little. But he'd probably
knock everything over.
- Plus, there's that big nose of his.
- That's not a nose, that's a horn.
- Is that so?
- His real nose is little.
I learn all kinds of things
being with you.
Okay, June bug, these are for you.
- What about the rest?
- The rest are for me.
No, they're not.
You're too old for balloons.
You're never too old for balloons.
Give me a hug.
I see your mama.
Don't keep her waiting.
- Bye, Pop-Pop.
- Bye, baby.
Hi, sweetie.
Did you have fun with Pop-Pop?
Please. Please, no.
Chow, you have anything
you wanna tell me?
Thank God you're here.
They keep me prisoner.
- They keep you prisoner.
- I don't do nothing for them ever.
They try and make me. I say, no.
They steal my chemicals.
I can't stop them. I am businessman.
You're a business...
The lady out front...
Hey, lady, are you still there?
Ask her if she's still there.
She says, yes.
How's her driving? Driving.
Is she good behind the wheel?
Good. She's good driver.
Licensed? Dependable?
She has a Camry.
Good.
The trucks will be here
first thing in the morning.
I strongly recommend
that you return our calls next time.
So have her drive you to the hospital.
She's gonna need her shoe.
- Where'd they cross?
- Laredo, looks like.
They didn't exactly send
their A players.
But like you said, it's cartel, all right.
Probing for weakness.
Well, they didn't find any.
What about Pinkman?
I'm making enquiries.
Yeah, that's two.
All right, let's close it up.
All right, bring it down.
You ready?
Okay, we're good.
You can take your mask off now.
Does that guy ever leave?
When exactly did that start?
It's new.
We had a...
We had a little drama
with the person you replaced.
- Sorry to hear that.
- No, it'll be fine.
Things will continue
to smooth out and...
Yeah, it'll be fine.
By the way, if you're at all worried
about working with me...
No, I'm not.
Whatever my shortcomings
last time...
...I intend for things to go perfectly
from here on out.
- So if there is...?
- Gale, you're great.
- Seriously.
- I just...
However you like things to be done
is exactly how we're gonna do them.
Period.
From here on out, so...
Please, teach me.
Okay.
Gale. It's good to see you.
Mr. Fring.
Wow, this is...
I should have called.
I'm not interrupting anything, am I?
No. No, no, not at all.
Please, come in.
Can I offer you something?
A crème de menthe?
No. No, thank you.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
Oh, no, no. It's no inconvenience.
I need to talk to you
about something.
Something rather pressing.
If push came to shove,
I was wondering...
...how soon you might be able
to take over the lab yourself.
You and an assistant.
Why would...?
- Why would push come to shove?
- Has Walter ever talked to you...
...about why he got into
this particular line of work?
I guess I assumed
it was because it pays so well.
It is, but specifically...
...has he... ever spoken to you
about his health problems?
I'm not surprised.
He's a very private person.
What exactly
are his health problems?
He's dying of cancer.
It is why he does this, to provide for
his family, which he's accomplished.
They will never want for anything,
he's seen to that.
How long does he have?
That is very much the question.
He does not wanna talk about it.
And every time I bring it up with him...
I don't know that he's fully accepted
the reality of it.
And not to sound cold-blooded,
but I am running a business here.
- No, I understand.
- I have a very large investment in this.
There's so much overhead
that I can't afford to shut down.
Not even for a week.
So you understand my concern.
And my desire for continuity.
I do. Absolutely.
Now, I intend to keep Walter on
as long as he wants...
...assuming that
he's physically up to it.
But as he cannot or will not tell me
how long that might be...
...I must prepare
for the worst-case scenario.
Well, worst-case scenario...
I suppose if we had...
...at least a few more cooks together.
You don't think you're ready now?
Well, I mean...
...he is such a...
A master.
There's always more for me to learn.
But I'm thinking that if we had...
...say...
...one or two more cooks.
One more...
...I guess would do it. I suppose.
I believe in you, Gale.
I know that when the time comes,
you will be ready.
What's up?
Walt, is there...?
Any particular trick
to purging the catalyst bed?
No, it's pretty straightforward.
I'll show you when we get there.
Yeah?
Tell him I'm in conference.
- I'm in conference.
- I'm looking to find a client of yours.
I was hoping you could help me out
with an address.
- Which client?
- Jesse Pinkman.
Jesse-Pinkman-in-the-phone-book
Jesse Pinkman.
How would one track him down,
I wonder.
- You're still here.
- I need your full attention, Saul.
Jesse Pinkman.
Current whereabouts.
The sooner you tell me, the sooner
you get back to whatever this is.
What am I, an 8th-grade hall monitor?
Current whereabouts.
- Let me tell you something, Mike, you...
- Whoa, you are good right there.
Now, let's both get comfortable.
Now, when I say,
I'm looking for Pinkman...
...we both know why, don't we?
You pretending otherwise only wastes
my time and se... s to annoy me.
Look, Mike...
...there are rules to this lawyer thing.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
Attorney-client privilege.
That's a big one.
That's something I provide for you.
So if I give up Pinkman...
...then you're gonna be asking,
"Saul gives them up pretty easy.
What's to keep him
from giving me up?" You see?
So then, where's the trust?
I trust the hole in the desert
I'd leave you in.
Yeah, that's an argument.
Saul...
...don't make me beat you
till your legs don't work.
Now tell me where to find him.
You know it's the right thing.
I can't tell you, Mike, all right? I...
Look, if I was to tell you, well, I just...
I couldn't live with myself.
I'm sorry.
But who's to say I didn't write
the address down in my day planner?
Or on a scratch piece of paper
somewhere?
Who's to say
I didn't write down a location...
...strictly for
my own professional use?
Do not touch anything on my desk.
I'm gonna leave the room,
make myself a Nescafé.
I'm just looking out for you, that's all.
Like a mother hen.
Money-laundering ain't what it used
to be. God, do I miss the... 80s.
You're wasting your time.
I'm buying the car wash, end of story.
Well, one look at this place,
you're gonna fall in love, so...
Was I right? Where... else you gonna find
a cash-only business that's this fun?
Unless we're talking massage parlours,
and, I don't see it. Shall we?
You ever actually play laser tag?
You know, it's good cardio.
Plus, you get to shoot at kids.
You got your bumper cars over there
down that way.
Got your arcade here,
all the latest video games.
Snack bar's there. Nothing stopping
you from selling beer to the parents.
- That's a whole new revenue stream...
- All right, already. We're good.
Holy Christ.
We're good? This constitutes good
where you're from?
- My car is bugged?
- I said, maybe. Maybe bugged.
I'm being followed?
What the hell have you gotten me into?
My own PI is threatening to break
my legs. That's like Thomas Magnum...
...threatening that little prissy guy
with the moustache.
Over and above.
Service-wise, this is over and above.
You and I survive this...
...I'm seriously rethinking
my pricing, yeah.
And that goes double for you,
Hip-Hop.
Okay, my guy's no dummy, right?
I give us maybe 24 hours before he
figures out that address goes nowhere.
You guys do your thing,
make it snappy.
I'll go see if they have".Tetris"
or something.
So how you holding up?
You?
I got my old job back.
At least until they kill me
and Gale takes over.
- So he's their boy, huh?
- He's their boy.
How long you think you've got?
Well, he asks a lot of questions
about the cooking process.
I try to be as vague as possible,
but I got that guy Victor watching me...
...listening to every word I say.
You know, maybe that the only thing
saving me is Gale's fastidiousness.
And once he feels confident
that he knows my entire method...
So, what do we do?
You know what we do.
There's got to be some other way.
Maybe it's better for you
to just go to the cops.
All right? I mean,
I can't believe I'm saying that and all...
...but for your family.
The DEA would love you,
all the shit you could tell them.
Federal witness protection,
that's a good deal.
As for me, I'll hit the road, yo.
I mean, I'll make it.
We had a good run.
But it's over.
Never the DEA.
The cook can't stop.
That's the one thing I'm certain of,
production cannot stop.
Gus can't afford to.
So if I'm the only chemist
that he's got...
...then I've got leverage,
and leverage keeps me alive.
It keeps you alive too.
I think I can see to that.
If I'm the only chemist that he's got.
I can't do it, Mr. White.
Like you said, I'm...
I'm not a...
I can't do it.
I'll do it.
I'm gonna need your help.
I mean,
they're watching me day and night.
They never leave me alone with Gale,
not for a moment.
Hell, I don't even know
where the man lives.
He's not in the phone book,
I can't find him on the Internet...
...and I can't do it in the lab,
Victor's always there.
But if I could just...
...shake Victor,
for even an hour one night...
...I think then that...
I may be able...
...to make it look like an accident.
There's got to be some other way.
I'm all ears.
But when it comes down to you and me
versus him, I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry...
...but it's gonna be him.
Now, you are the only edge
that I've got...
...as long as they don't know
that you're in town.
But I need you to track him,
get me his address.
And I'll do the rest.
Look, I saved your life, Jesse.
Are you gonna save mine?
Yeah?
Please, tell me you found him.
6353 Juan Tabo Boulevard.
Apartment 6.
- You there?
- Yeah.
6353 Juan Tabo. Number 6. Got it.
- He's home?
- Yep.
Anyone watching the place?
No. Looks pretty much wide-open.
When are you gonna do it?
Tonight.
Once it gets dark.
Don't do this, Mr. White.
Please. Go to the cops.
We got a problem.
Some kind of chemical leaking
in your lab.
Better come with me.
I'll follow you.
They tell me to bring you, I bring you.
Come on, get in the car.
I don't know if it's a barrel leak...
...but you got something
mighty stinky down there.
After you.
Walter, the sooner you figure out what
this is, the sooner we all go home.
Please, don't do this.
Mike...
...you don't have to do this.
Yeah, unfortunately, I do, Walter.
Downstairs.
I'll cook. I'll cook for free. There won't
be any more trouble, I promise you.
- No.
- Lf I could talk to Gus...
...I can make him understand.
If I could talk to Gus,
I can convince him.
Just let me, please... Please.
- Please, let me talk to him.
- Shut up! Shut up.
I can't do it. I'm sorry.
I'll give you Jesse Pinkman.
Like you said, he's the problem.
He's always been the problem.
And without him, we would...
And he's in town, all right?
He's not in Virginia
or wherever you're looking.
He's right here in Albuquerque
and I could take you to him.
I'll take you right to him.
- What do you say?
- Where is he?
- Right now, you give me an address.
- I don't... He moves. He moves around.
But if you let me call him...
No, no, please.
No, I just... My phone. I'll just...
It's just my phone. I'll call him
and I'll have him meet me.
All right? Okay?
Okay?
Did you do it?
Mr. White?
No, I didn't do it.
I can't now.
- It's gonna have to be you.
- What? No way, man.
You're closer than we are.
You'll have a 20-minute lead.
They've got me,
they're going to kill me.
- Jesse, do it now! Do it!
- Son of a bitch!
Do it, Jesse! Do it!
Just what the hell was that exactly?
You might wanna hold off.
Yeah?
- Why?
- Because your boss is gonna need me.
6353 Juan Tabo, Apartment 6.
Yeah.
Hi. How can I help you?
Take whatever you want.
I have money. I have...
I got a lot of money.
I have...
Please, don't do this.
You don't... You...
You... You don't have to do this.
www.tvsubtitles.net