Come on.
Come....
Come on. Come on, baby.
Please, please. Come on, come on.
Come on!
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
Yeah.
Slow down. Slow-- Slow down.
And just-- Just take a deep breath.
Do it.
All right.
Now, what happened?
All right. All right. Now...
...listen-- Listen to me.
Are you listening?
Everything is gonna be okay.
I promise.
No, no-- Listen. Calm down.
Just....
Sit tight. I know who to call.
Saul Goodman sent me.
Come on. Inside.
Watch the door.
Where is she?
Any other drugs in the house?
Think hard.
Your freedom depends on it.
What about guns?
You got any guns in the house?
Here's your story.
You woke up. You found her.
That's all you know.
Say it.
Say it, please. "I woke up. I found her.
That's all I know."
Say it. "I woke up. I found her.
I woke up. I found her.
That's all I know.
Again.
I woke up. I found her.
That's all I know.
Again. Again.
I woke up. I found her.
That's all I know.
Once you call,
the people who show up...
...will be with
the Office of Medical Investigations.
That's primarily who you'll talk to.
Police officers may arrive,
they may not.
Depends on how busy
a morning they're having.
Typically, ODs are not
a high-priority call.
There's nothing to incriminate you...
...so I'd be amazed
if you got placed under arrest.
However, if you do, you say nothing.
You tell them
you just want your lawyer.
Then you call Saul Goodman.
And do I need to state the obvious?
I was not here.
You put on a long-sleeved shirt...
...and cover
those track marks on your arm.
Count down from 20,
and then you dial.
Hang tough.
You're in the home stretch.
Do you want 2-percent or skim?
-Two.
-Two. All right.
Thank you.
Junior.
-Flynn.
-What?
Flynn.
I'll be there in a minute.
You all right?
Flynn, get your butt in here.
Oh, my God. Mom, Dad, come here.
You gotta see this.
Seriously.
-What?
-Look right there. Look at that.
Are those donations?
-Yes.
-Actual donations for your dad?
Total strangers gave us $490.
Twenty-six people.
Virginia, Minnesota, Montana.
Look at this one. Vancouver.
All the way up in Canada.
And it's all real, actual money.
It's actually right there
in the PayPal account.
And look what they're saying.
"Hang in there, Walt." "Good luck."
"Hang in there."
Isn't this awesome?
That's-- Wow, that is something.
Walt, don't you think
a little thank-you is in order?
Yes, absolutely. Thank you, son.
Thank you. This is a big, big help.
Oh, look, 20 more bucks
from Thunder Bay, Ontario.
Damn. Five hundred and ten dollars.
If you're trying to sell me something,
I've got four words for you.:
"Do-not-call list."
However, if you're cool,
leave it at the beep.
How did I know you wouldn't be
answering your phone?
I'm on my way.
I'm gonna be there momentarily.
I expect you on the porch, bag packed,
ready to go. No excuses.
Sir, you may not wanna
be here for this.
I just woke up and I found her.
That's all I know.
What's her date of birth?
Sir, your daughter's date of birth?
April....
-April 4th, 1982.
-Okay.
And mother's maiden name
and place of birth.
-My mother?
-Your daughter's mother.
Bishop.
-And place of birth?
-Phoenix.
Phoenix, Arizona?
This is our address.
Do you have someone
who can drive you?
I can drive.
Well, then if you'd like
to meet us there...
...we can complete the intake
and take our samples...
...and then you can make
your arrangements.
Okay?
Now, do you need a card?
Will you both be coming?
I don't believe it.
Walt, you have to see this.
-Forty from Te--
-Terre Haute.
Walt.
It's me.
Are you there? Hello.
I'm just checking in.
Our friend says
he thinks everything went well.
That's-- That's good.
So listen. Just call me, all right?
Hey, Walt, you've gotta come in here.
We just broke a thousand dollars.
All right. I'm coming.
Some of you already know
my brother-in-law. He's a good man.
The doctors say this operation
has a real chance of helping him.
They're also saying they wanna
be paid in private islands, so dig deep.
Biggest donation...
...gets a six-pack
of my very own Schraderbrau.
Home-brewed to silky perfection.
Smallest donation
gets two six-packs.
All right. Other than Gomie here
pees sitting down...
...here's what we know.
Christian Ortega, a.k.a. Combo.
Shot dead
by an unknown assailant last month.
"Combo?" I hear you say.
"Why, I'm unfamiliar with that name.
Was he a Nobel laureate perchance?"
No. He was a dipshit
wannabe banger.
Now, no arrests,
save for stealing a baby Jesus...
...from a Knights of Columbus manger
back when he was 17.
This dude was so low-rep,
he never showed up on our radar.
So why am I talking about him?
Anyone? Anyone?
Bueller?
-He was dealing Blue Sky.
-That's right.
Now, how is it that the purest,
most professional grade...
...of meth we've ever come across
is being slung by the likes of that?
But wait. It gets better.
Since baby-Jesus thief there
slowed a bullet with his neck...
...the blue stuff's
vanished from town, okay?
Not a speck to be found
in Albuquerque. Now, why is that?
Well, because maybe
your Heisenberg's in prison.
So says A.P.D.
They think they got their man.
I know you don't buy it,
but maybe it's true.
James Edward Kilkelly, yeah.
A.P.D. thinks this is our mastermind.
You believe that,
I got a bridge to sell you.
-He copped to it, didn't he?
-For an extra pudding cup...
...every night at Los Lunas?
Maybe if you give him
a pack of cigarettes...
...he'll tell you what
he did with Jimmy Hoffa. No, no, no.
I've been thinking.
Top-shelf product like this?
It doesn't fall off the face of the earth.
Raw talent's bound
to pop up somewhere.
It's like Whack-A-Mole.
So I've been making phone calls.
Local police departments,
small-town sheriffs.
Haven't had much luck
inside the Land of Enchantment.
But outside,
I've got reports of the blue stuff...
...making a scene here in Texas,
Arizona, Colorado and Nevada.
In fact, everywhere but here.
Almost as if somebody wised up,
stopped shitting where they eat.
Now...
...I say Heisenberg's still out there.
I say he's gone regional.
Only he's still right here in town.
Come on, 2800.
Come on, big 28. You can do it.
Only 30 more dollars. Thirty more.
Fo-- Forty dollars! Twenty-eight ten.
-Yes!
Who's gonna be next?
Your guy found him?
Where is he?
Okay, listen.
No, no, I don't care.
You have your guy pick--
Saul. Just shut-- Saul.
Saul, shut up
and give me the address.
I don't recommend it.
A.P.D.'s been known
to sit on this place...
..keep an eye
on the comings and goings.
Are they here now?
Well, I don't see any sign,
but that's the point.
Police could be the least of it.
You could just get mugged or shot.
How about you go on home, Walter?
Let me handle this.
Yo.
Jesse.
Jesse. Jesse. Look at me, son.
-Wake up. Wake up.
-Hey.
I ain't got nothing for you, man.
It's all gone.
Jesse, damn it, wake up. Just--
Jesse, Jesse. Jesse, it's me.
Okay, it's me. It's Walt. It's Walt.
Jesse.
-Yeah.
-Come on, let's get out of here.
No, no, no.
-I'm good.
-Come on. Help me out now.
I'm good. I'm good.
Right here, man. Right here.
Listen, Jesse, you are not good
right here.
You are not good at all. You hear?
Now, you just put your arms
around me. Come on.
You're gonna stand up...
...and we're gonna
walk out of here, okay?
We're gonna take you
someplace nice and safe.
That's it. Now, let's go.
Come on. Here we go.
I killed her.
-What?
-I killed her. It was me.
-I killed her, man. I killed her.
-No.
Jesse, look at me. Look at me.
You didn't kill anybody.
I loved her.
I loved her more than anything.
No, no. No.
I haven't given much thought
to the programs.
I guess they should be....
I don't know.
Just use your best judgement.
There's no yellow dress here.
It's all-- It's all black and grey.
When's the last time you saw her
ever wearing a yellow dress?
What about blue?
Blue's better than black, right?
No, no. Not dark blue. More like....
Not super-bright, either.
I mean, blue is blue.
No. No cleavage.
Long sleeves.
Yeah. It's nice.
It's nice.
Big yawn, Holly.
I know what you feel like.
I'm tired too.
-Okay, sweetie.
-Yes.
Yes!
Here we go.
Here we go. Yes.
Would you mind
turning that thing down or off?
Junior. Hey.
The dinging.
Just turn down the volume.
-Dad, it's money.
-Just please do it.
Okay, the noise
is disturbing the baby.
Marie, slow down. I can't--
Oh, my God. You are kidding me.
Sure. Of course.
Any day after school.
Okay. Wait. I'm gonna-- Let me tell him,
and I'll call you right back.
Okay.
-Guess what.
-What?
-You are gonna be in the newspaper.
-No way.
One of Marie's patients
works at the Journal.
She told him about the website
and the donations...
...and they're gonna do a story
about you.
-For real?
-Yep.
They're coming to interview you
with a photo and everything.
Awesome.
-It'll mean more hits.
-And more contributions.
East of Scottsdale?
Let me guess. Not talking.
Nope. Not a one.
Someone somewhere
is running one tight ship.
All right, chief. Yeah. Thanks a lot.
Yeah. You too.
Agent Schrader,
can you spare a moment?
Yes, sir. Absolutely.
Gentlemen, this is
Supervising Agent Hank Schrader.
Agent Schrader, I'd like you to meet
Andrew Coffman of the Adobe Hotel.
-Nice to meet you.
Paul Canterna
of Canterna Real Estate.
-Hey, it's a pleasure.
-Good to meet you.
And Gustavo Fring
of Los Pollos Hermanos.
-Please, just Gus.
-Hi, Gus.
You guys make some killer chicken.
Thank you very much.
These gentlemen are underwriting
this year's Fun Run...
...and I thought
I would give them a tour.
Absolutely. Get to see
what you're supporting. Thank you.
Can you tell us a little
about your work here?
Yes, the Albuquerque office...
...covers everything
from drug-related money laundering...
...to interdiction of illicit substances
crossing the border.
Now, the group that I supervise
focuses on methamphetamine...
...which is a growing problem
in the country, unfortunately.
-Terrible.
-Yeah. It is indeed.
We've had
some successes locally...
...but overall,
the supply seems to be growing.
I gotta tell you, community outreach,
like this Fun Run...
...one of the most powerful
weapons we have.
Anything we can do.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, Hank.
-Gentlemen.
-Thanks.
Sure. Thank you.
Is this one of your agents?
Oh, yeah, no, no,
that's my brother-in-law.
He's got a health issue.
We're trying to--
Oh, I'm very sorry.
What sort of health issue?
-Lung cancer.
-Oh, that's a rough one.
-Oh, hey, you don't have to do that.
-Please. Please. I'm happy to do it.
-Thank you very much.
-You're welcome.
Just so you know,
I won't be back for a while.
I'm gonna have
my surgery on Friday.
I'm hopeful it'll go well.
But if not,
Saul will take care of things.
He's got your money.
He's keeping it for you.
Look, Jesse, lingering on things
doesn't help, believe me.
Just try and focus
on getting better, okay.
I deserve this.
What?
What you said in the desert.
I get it, what you meant.
I deserve whatever happens.
Oh, shit.
There he is!
Walt, they're doing a feature
on Walter Jr.
We called you about 50 times.
Marie, I thought we were just talking
about a newspaper story.
I know. But I thought, you know,
if it's good enough for the Journal...
...then why not TV? So I went for it.
-This is him?
-Yes.
This is Dad. Great.
Let's get everyone on the couch.
I'm thinking Walt Jr. in the middle...
...Mom and Dad on either side.
Mom and Dad?
How much money
have you raised so far?
Six thousand, three hundred
and sixty dollars.
But there's more coming in
all the time.
-Wow, that's amazing.
-We don't even know what to say.
It's just-- It's been incredible.
Judging from things you have
written about him...
-...your dad must be quite a guy.
-Yeah. He is. He's the best.
You don't wanna lose him,
do you, Walter?
None of us do. We love him.
-He's a good man, isn't he?
-Absolutely. Ask anyone.
Anybody. He's a great father,
a great teacher.
He knows everything there is
to know about chemistry.
He's patient with you,
and he's always there for you.
He's just decent.
And he always does the right thing.
And that's how he teaches me to be.
-Would you say he's your hero?
-Oh, yeah. Yes, ma'am. Totally.
My dad is my hero.
Does that put him to sleep?
This one just relaxes him a little.
We're almost ready.
We'll be taking you in, in just a minute.
Okay. Thank you.
Well....
-Here we are.
-Yeah.
Relaxed yet?
As a matter of fact....
I don't know what this stuff is,
but it's pretty great.
Yeah, it looks like it.
We'll be here when you wake up.
Well, I'll be looking for you.
They'll probably want me
to take your glasses.
Yeah, you better.
Yeah, okay. Okay. I got them.
Where's your phone?
Your cell phone. Did you bring it?
Which one?
I'm pretty sure
he didn't bring it, Mom.
Okay.
Well, first things first.
How old is that baby now?
When do I get to meet her?
I was actually thinking
of bringing her today, but....
She's 7 weeks tomorrow.
-Seven, right?
-Yeah.
Yeah, oh, hey, I have a picture...
...here somewhere.
-She's beautiful.
-Thanks.
Always a relief to say that
and actually mean it.
-How's your pain level, Walter?
-It's....
Very low, basically.
Shortness of breath?
-A bit, but much better.
-Good.
Well, your margins look good.
I can't foresee the future...
...but even
conservatively speaking...
...I can say that you bought yourself
some real time here.
There's no reason
not to be optimistic.
That's great.
That is great. Thank you, doctor.
So when could he get back
to his normal routine?
-He can ease into it now.
-Okay.
-And can he go back to work or...?
-I'd give it a few more weeks.
Make sure you avoid any heavy lifting
and continue to get plenty of rest.
But he can be on his own?
I mean, just more,
you know, independent.
Yes. Use your best judgement.
Well....
Now, that's good news
for you, huh, honey?
One less baby in the house.
-Don, hey.
-Hey, Stew.
Hey, welcome back.
Thanks. It's good to be back.
Jesus. We were all so sorry to hear.
Yes. Thanks.
Terrible thing. Just....
But, you know, we've all been
thinking about you, and....
-You been doing okay?
-I'm doing okay.
After a certain point,
time off doesn't help...
...so I figured I'd rather be here.
-Focus on work.
-Sure. Absolutely.
Yeah.
Well, see you inside.
Continue to descend through 1500.
Headed downwind for a left base
on Runway 17.
Number 26-Tango,
descend to maintain 13,000.
Truth or Consequences altimeter,
two-niner-niner-eight.
Pima 311, contact
Albuquerque Center 134.6.
Juliet-5-Bravo, ident, say altitude.
Juliet-5-Bravo, roger.
Clear direct to Winslow.
I think I may just keep this.
Sky?
What do you think?
Doesn't look so bad, right?
What are you doing?
I'm going to Hank and Marie's
for the weekend.
-Since when?
-I'm taking the baby with me.
Marie will pick up
Walter Jr. from school.
You'll have the house to yourself
for two days.
I want you to pack your things
and leave.
Why would I do that?
Hank has offered to help. You shouldn't
be doing any heavy lifting.
-Skyler.
-I want you gone by Monday morning.
I want--
I want you gone.
Okay. Can you at least tell me why?
Because you're a liar, Walt.
Two cell phones, after all.
What?
Before your surgery, I asked
if you had packed your cell phone...
...and you said, "Which one?"
When?
Skyler, I was medicated.
I mean, I could have said
the world was flat.
You know what I think?
I think you accidentally
told the truth.
Honey, we have been over this.
Asked and answered, right?
Then it got me thinking again...
...about all the strange behaviour.
Not the least of which
was the disappearance.
Out of my mind with worry,
calling hospitals...
...checking the morgue.
Your fugue state?
I had to believe that, didn't I?
I had to find a way.
I mean, who would lie
about such a thing?
You tell me, Skyler.
You tell me exactly what it is
you think I'm lying about.
What? I'm having an affair.
Is that what you think?
Yeah. For the last few weeks.
With whom?
Who am I having an affair with?
Well, my guess
was Gretchen Schwartz.
Something was going on between you.
I just knew.
Jesus. Skyler. Get me a Bible
to swear on, if that's what it takes.
I am not having an affair
with Gretchen.
I know. I know you're not.
Because I asked her.
It really took me forever
to get in touch with her.
She was ducking my calls for weeks.
So I finally left a message:
"What exactly is going on
between you and my husband?"
I thought that'd get her attention,
and it did.
So she called me back,
and she finally told me.
The money for your treatment...
...Gretchen and Elliott
didn't give you a dime.
They paid for nothing.
You refused every offer
they made you.
But that didn't make sense...
...because I checked with Delcavoli
and the hospital...
...and not including your surgery...
...we're nearly paid up.
Over $100,000.
Out of where? Out of thin air?
But then...
...I called your mother.
Yeah.
Thanks for that too.
But I thought, you know,
maybe she has some money...
...that I don't know about.
Maybe she contributed.
It's possible.
It turns out that not only is the money
not from your mother...
...she didn't even know
that you have cancer.
You never went to see her.
I dropped you at the airport.
I picked you up.
You were gone for four days...
...and yet she swears...
...that you were never there.
Lies on top of lies on top of lies.
Skyler.
Could you...
...just once...
...do me the courtesy
of not denying it?
Skyler.
Skyler, don't do this, please.
I....
Skyler, please don't go.
If I tell you the truth, will you stay?
Stay, and I will tell you everything.
Whatever it is...
...I'm afraid to know.
Wayfarer-515, radio check.
Wayfarer-515,
Albuquerque Center, roger.
Climb and maintain 13,000.
Juliet-Mike-21, squawk 4201, ident.
Juliet-Mike-21...
...climb and maintain 17,000.
Clear direct to Albuquerque via the--
Aircraft calling, please stand by.
Jane-Mike-21, turn, heading--
Disregard.
Aircraft calling, say again.
Lifeguard-46,
clear direct Albuquerque...
...climb and maintain 17 000.
Juliet-Mike-21, turn left,
heading 115.
Wayfarer-515...
...traffic 3 o'clock, KingAir,
turn left, heading 085.
Sierra-alpha-alpha...
...contact Albuquerque Center, 134.6.
Contact Albuquerque Center, 134.6.
Wayfarer-515, descend to 10,000.
Juliet-Mike-21, do you have that traffic
at your 9 o'clock?
Wayfarer-515,
do you have that traffic?
www.tvsubtitles.net