Let's break it down.
Hydrogen. What does that give us?
By mole, we're looking at 63 percent.
Sixty-three?
That is a big bite.
- My next step's gotta be oxygen.
- Oxygen, 26 percent.
Twenty-six.
There you have your water.
- Carbon, 9 percent.
- Carbon, 9.
- For a total of 98 percent.
- Right.
- Nitrogen, 1.25 percent.
- One-point-two-five.
That brings you to 99 and a quarter.
Which only leaves you
with the trace elements...
...down where the magic happens.
Oh, wait a minute. What about calcium?
Calcium's not a trace.
Got a whole skeleton to account for.
- You would think, right?
- Right.
Calcium.
Calcium's only 0.25 percent.
What? That low? Seriously?
Damn, I never would've thought that.
- Okay, so where does iron fit in?
- Iron.
Well, okay, 0.00004 percent.
What? You can't have
haemoglobin without iron.
- Apparently, it don't take much.
- No doubt. Go figure.
- Sodium.
- Sodium, 0.04.
- Phosphorus, 0.19.
- Point-one-nine.
There we go.
So the whole thing...
...adds up to 99.888042 percent.
We are 0.111958 percent...
...shy.
- Supposedly, that's everything.
- Yeah?
I don't know, I just...
It seems like something's missing,
doesn't it?
There's got to be more
to a human being than that.
I hate these shoes.
Shoes make me look like
I should be changing bedpans...
...like I should be squeaking around...
...bringing soup to some
disgusting old person...
...then take the bus home
to my 16 cats.
Then why are you wearing them?
I like the support. My arches
happen to be extremely archy.
Yo, what's up? Hey, can you call me,
like, in two minutes? Thanks, bye.
I gotta go take this.
Female?
Louis.
Not like it's any
of your business, though.
- Just be quick about it.
- No.
Oh, and please don't say, "Yo. "
You can't know how much I hate that.
You missed a spot, right there.
Should you be on that ladder?
You're more than welcome
to take over for me in here.
I don't see why you don't get
Walt to do it.
Yeah, there's an idea.
So I'm working on
this new short story...
...and there's this stoner character in it
and I'm trying to...
Well, you know, actually,
let me back up.
You smoked your fair share of pot
in college, didn't you?
I mean, you at least tried it.
Come on.
I perhaps tried it. Why?
Do you remember it
having an effect on your mood?
Like, changing it in any major way?
It made me more serious.
Really?
Because I mostly remember it made me
light-headed, that's about it.
I was just wondering
if it maybe could...
You know, it's just a character thing
I'm stuck on. Never mind.
- Walter Jr. 's on pot?
- What? No.
No. No.
- What would make you even...?
- Where's he getting it?
- Marie.
- Seriously. Is it this Louis person?
- What are you gonna do about this?
- Marie, you need to look me in the eye.
I am strictly asking about a story
that I'm writing, that's all.
Right hand to God,
Walter Jr. Is not on pot...
...certainly not as far as I know.
Not as far as you know?
Marie.
Hey, look at me.
Hey, turn around and look at me.
This here.
I wouldn't do this
to my worst enemy.
This is degrading.
I'm sorry.
You hope I'll make it easy
and just drop dead, don't you?
But I won't.
So either kill me, or let me go.
You don't have it in you, Walter.
How do you know my name?
Jesse. He told Emilio and me.
I came by to sell your meth.
So what? You threaten him, huh?
Did you beat it out of him?
Not even close.
What else did he tell you?
Pretty much everything
he could think of.
You were his high school teacher.
One time you taught
about carbon dioxide...
...by making grape soda in class.
You have a son who's retarded,
or in a wheelchair or something.
It shouldn't come across
as some news flash.
That partner of yours...
...he's got a big mouth.
Walter...
...I don't know what you think
you're doing here...
...but trust me...
...this line of work doesn't suit you.
So I should just let you go, then.
Just unlock you and... adiós, huh?
I don't see
what other choice you have.
It's between that
and cold-blooded murder.
Besides...
...your real problem's
sitting upstairs.
Occupied.
Hey, yo, I'm trying to pinch one off
in here.
Just give me some privacy,
would you?
- Okay.
- What the hell, man?
What are you doing, man?
- You asshole. What...?
- You told him my name.
- Says who, him?
- My name, where I work.
- You told him about my son.
- Hey, don't touch me.
- You damn junkie.
- No, give me that. That's mine.
This is going down the toilet.
Watch it go.
No, that's worth 40 grand, you...
It's worth nothing
when you smoke it all.
Get off the toilet.
- Get off the toilet!
- No.
Get off the toilet.
Stop it.
No. No way.
No.
No, no, no.
Jesse, where the hell do you think
you're going?
Back off, man, Jesus.
- We've got work to do.
- No, no.
You got work to do. I did my part.
You mean that obscenity
I spent hours cleaning up?
- That is your contribution?
- Kiss my pink ass, man.
I didn't ask for any of this. How am I
supposed to live here now, huh?
My whole house smells like
toe cheese and dry cleaning.
Because you didn't follow
my instructions.
Oh, well, Heil Hitler, bitch.
And let me tell you something else.
We flipped a coin, okay?
You and me. You and me.
Coin flip is sacred.
Your job is waiting for you
in that basement...
...as per the coin.
Fucking do it, already.
That's what she said. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I think
we have some of those.
- Yeah, you'll have to try them on.
- Hello?
- Seven and a half, maybe. I don't know.
- Excuse me.
Do you have these in black?
Anyways, so like I was saying...
...I went to the party the other night.
Yeah, Tony was there.
Whatever.
Hey, where have you been?
I called you two hours ago.
Sorry, baby, I'm kind of busy here.
What's up?
Well, kind of a lot, actually,
and it's a delicate subject.
- So I need you to focus, and...
- Hey, sit down! Sit down!
Damn it, Hank.
I'm sorry, babe, I'm just in the middle
of something here.
Get down. Get down.
Sit down! Sit your ass down,
comprende? You too, sit down!
I'm back, babe. What's up?
- Walter Jr.
- Yeah, what about him?
Marijuana. He's smoking it.
Excuse me, his own mother
seems to think so.
- Skyler told you that?
- She inferred it.
She inferred it, huh?
She strongly inferred it.
Like, " Doctor, my friend suffers
from erectile dysfunction. "
- Please, come on.
- All right.
- Talk to him.
- Walt should talk to him.
Skyler, better yet.
She'll kick his butt.
I think it ought to be you.
You know, tell him
some horror stories.
Maybe show him
some autopsy pictures.
An autopsy of a pot overdose?
Come on.
I don't know, baby,
it's just that, you know...
...I figure his dad should be the one
doing this, don't you think?
Hank, he respects you.
Yeah, all right. Well, listen, yeah,
I'll swing by their place after work.
- Good. Scare him straight.
- Yeah, yeah.
Hey, where's my sugar?
Excuse me, ma'am.
Ma'am, you need to be wearing footies
before you try those on.
I'm extremely clean.
Yeah, well, I'd really appreciate it.
Hey, sorry about that.
Yeah, I'll check.
You know, I hid a pair for you
last week, grey ones.
- What do you think?
- About what?
This look like a nice place?
No, not really.
Think you'd like to live here?
No.
- Sure about that?
- Yeah, pretty sure.
I thought we were going to
Cold Stone Creamery.
Yeah, yeah, well,
we took a little detour.
Figure we'll come over
and check out how the other half lives.
This here is what we call
the Crystal Palace.
You know who lives in the palace?
Meth-heads.
Nasty, skeevy meth-heads...
...who'd sell their grandma's coochie
for a hit.
Oh, you think that's funny?
That's funny, huh? Yeah.
Let me tell you something.
Every one of these...
...miserable wastes of skin
got started how?
- How do you think they started?
- I don't know.
What do you think they were doing
before they graduated...
...to shooting meth in their dicks?
A gateway drug.
That's what we call it.
Dollars to doughnuts,
and I shit you not...
...that gateway drug was marijuana,
every time.
- You understand?
- Yeah.
So why are you telling me this?
Because I love you,
you little bastard.
And, hey, I was young once,
you know.
The world's a messed up place,
You know, just this one time,
you know...
Hey! Hey! Hey, you!
Yeah, you, princess. Get over here.
Hey, don't make me
get out of the car.
Check this out.
What I'm talking about.
- I ain't holding, okay?
- Did I say open your mouth?
And hands off the car.
Other side. Go around the other side,
talk to my friend here.
What's your name, sweetheart?
- Wendy.
- Wendy, huh?
How much you charge
for a windy, Wendy?
- I ain't doing him, he's a kid.
- Jesus, was that my question?
Don't think so hard,
it's gonna hurt your brain.
- Are you on the pipe or on the needle?
- Nothing. Neither.
Yeah, yeah.
Show us your teeth, huh?
Come on, Wendy,
let's see those pearly whites.
Oh, God. See that? Pipe, definitely.
Big time, big time on the pipe.
You got something
you wanna ask Wendy?
No, not really.
You ever smoke anything else,
Wendy?
Sausages don't count.
Seriously, tell my friend here
how you got started.
Probably used to be, what? Like a
Girl Scout, or sang in the church choir.
- What are you, like, handicapped?
- He broke his leg playing football.
He's a qb. Got an arm like a howitzer.
So tell me, Wendy, you smoke pot?
Why, you got some?
No. Right, hoof it, get lost.
Get out of here.
Hey, fair warning, next time
I'm gonna bust you.
So, what do you think?
Cool.
Shut the door. Shut the door.
Lock it. Lock it, lock it.
Who the hell was that?
Cop and some football player
messing with me.
They ask about me, huh?
No, I think they just wanted pot.
Right there.
Shit, I left my root beer.
- Hello?
- Hey, sweetie, it's me.
Listen, I'm so sorry.
Time, it just completely got away
from me. I'm just...
My fault, my fault.
Bogdan just kept me here late...
...you know, doing some inventory...
...and I should've just...
You know, you're right.
I gotta learn to say, you know, "No. "
But...
Sky? You there?
You're at the car wash?
Yeah.
I seriously doubt that,
since you quit two weeks ago.
I called Bogdan, looking for you.
Quite an earful he gave me.
Listen...
Listen, I'll come home
and we'll talk about it.
- I don't think so, Walt.
- Honey...
Wherever you are...
...why don't you just
stay there tonight?
Skyler?
Walter?
Hello?
Hey, there's a hungry guy here.
Come on.
Damn.
I didn't think you were coming back.
How long was I out?
Ten, 15 minutes?
I've never seen someone knock
themselves out just by coughing.
Were you on the same shit
you used on me?
I've got lung cancer.
I'll make you another sandwich.
It's safe.
There's no poison.
Because that would be
the way to do it...
...if you're gonna do it.
I suppose it would.
You being a chemist and all.
So that name...
...Krazy-8.
Do I really have to call you that?
I mean, no offence, but...
...don't you have a real name?
Domingo.
That's "Sunday," right?
I'd rather call you that,
if you don't mind.
I can't say I ever liked it much.
So, Domingo...
...you from around town here
or someplace else?
Hey, Walter?
You getting to know me...
...is not gonna make it easier
for you to kill me.
Not that I mind, you understand?
You know, you keep telling me
that I don't have it in me.
Well, maybe.
But maybe not.
I sure as hell am looking for
any reason not to.
I mean, any good reason at all.
Sell me.
Tell me what it is.
I'd start off by promising
that if you let me go...
...I won't come after you,
that you'd be safe.
I guess I'd say
what happened between us...
...never happened.
And what's best for both parties
is we forget all about it.
But you know anybody in my situation
would make promises like that.
And, in my case,
they happen to be true.
You'll never know for sure.
So, what else can I tell you?
I don't know.
But you've gotta convince me.
And you're going nowhere
until you do.
- Hey, yeah.
- Yeah.
I'm from here in town, man.
ABQ, born and bred.
Never left.
Studied Business Administration
over at UNM...
...got my degree.
Really?
Does that come in handy
in the drug trade?
Doesn't hurt.
I was gonna study music originally.
Maybe even try out
for Oberlin and Berklee.
My pops talked me out of it.
Said there was no money in it unless
I wind up some bullshit rock star...
...and I hadn't a snowball chance
at that one.
What does your dad do?
He owns Tampico Furniture
over on Menaul.
Wait a minute, I know that place.
Wait a minute. That's...
That's that...
They used to have those late-night...
- The stupid commercials.
- That they had, yeah.
Yeah, that's him.
Been doing them for over 30 years.
Wait a minute.
How did it go? It was...
Wait, wait, wait. It was...
Don't let shopping
Strain your brain-o
Just sing this short refrain-o
- Our furniture is bueno
- Tampico is the name- o
Pretty moronic. But what can you do?
Well, it did tend
to stick in your head.
Did you write that?
Being the musician in the family.
Oh, no, man.
It was my crazy uncle Alex.
He sings it at bars,
trying to pick up on women.
His mind, it's like saying,
"Hey, I wrote 'Stairway to Heaven. "'
Yeah, but at Tampico Furniture, I...
I think when my son was born
that we bought his bassinet there.
We don't sell bassinets there.
It's more of a speciality item.
We did use to sell cribs.
A crib, then, okay. A crib.
Yeah. No, I remember that.
In fact, I remember recognising
your dad from those commercials.
Although, he wasn't anywhere near
as friendly in real life.
Yeah. No shit.
Did he try selling you
that extended warranty?
Yeah, he probably did.
And I was probably dumb enough
to buy it.
Yeah, that was his big thing.
You ask him for a glass of water...
...he'd tell you you need
an extended warranty on the ice.
- Did you work there too?
- Only my whole life.
Up until the day I said,
"Fuck you," and quit.
So...
...16 years ago,
how old would you have been?
If it was after school,
trust me, I was there.
Might have even helped ring you up.
You and your extended warranty
on the crib.
Small world.
It is.
The paths we take, huh?
Jesse know you've got cancer?
No one but you.
- Not your family?
- No.
Why not?
Not a conversation
that I'm even remotely ready to have.
That's why you're cooking meth?
You wanna leave money
for your family.
Hell.
I'll write you a cheque right now
if you let me go.
Like I said, Walter...
...if this line of work
doesn't suit you...
...get out before it's too late.
I don't know what to do.
You do.
I'll get the key.
No.
Oh, no, no, no.
No. No, don't do this.
Don't do this.
Why are you doing this?
You're doing the right thing, Walter.
Do you wanna?
So you're not angry?
Angry at you?
Live and let live, man.
That's very understanding.
Whatever, man.
I just wanna go home.
Me too.
Unlock me, Walter.
The moment I do...
...are you gonna stick me
with that broken piece of plate?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Hello?
Anybody down here?
Everybody...
...I need you all to take your seats.
Settle down, please. Thank you.
I understand
that Mr. White is feeling...
...a little under the weather
this morning.
So you folks are going to have
to be making do with me today.
And we are going to be watching
a very interesting video...
...on carbon.
Very important stuff.
- So, what do you think?
- It's a cook site. Gotta be.
Nobody came way the hell out here
just to buy.
Fire there could have started
by accident.
I don't think that was meant
to destroy evidence.
Got a couple of Dooley tracks
headed away, towards the road.
So, what, they're in
some sort of camper-slash-lab?
They accidentally start a fire
and everybody FOs?
Yeah. Why not?
So why did that little hair-gelled shit
leave his car?
- Gomey, it's a culture in decline.
- It's a rich and vibrant culture.
It's a car that jumps up and down.
What the hell?
You people used to be conquistadors,
for chrissake.
Smells like a Drakkar Noir
factory in here.
I already searched it.
Yeah.
You're wasting your time.
Give it up. If this here's a trap car,
it's gonna take more...
...than your dumb white ass to find it.
- Oh, yeah?
You are talking to the trap-car master,
my friend.
I'm Rain Man counting
his toothpicks.
Yeah, you're like Rain Man. Retarded.
Yeah, baby.
- Hello, zippy.
- Asshole.
Sort of looks like meth
but it's too damn white.
You know what I'm thinking, Gomey?
Yep. Somebody croaked our snitch.
Hey, agent.
You got something?
I don't know.
It just... Doesn't it seem like...
...something's missing?
What about the soul?
The soul.
There's nothing but chemistry here.
Skyler?
There's something I have to tell you.
www.tvsubtitles.net